Guide to the Randolph Horton papers, 1877-1928.
Horton, Randolph papers, 1877-1928.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Randolph Horton papers, 1877-1928.
1799
Randolph Horton, 1850-1929.
2 cubic ft.
Legal papers, correspondence, and other papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Primarily legal papers pertaining to various cases over which Judge Horton presided while Justice of the New York State Supreme Court, 6th Judicial District or as a private attorney; also, correspondence and papers (1917-1919) relating to the Ithaca Calendar Clock Company, of which Horton was a trustee, mainly in connection with its going into receivership and with its dissolution.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Lawyer, judge, mayor of Ithaca, New York.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Primarily legal papers pertaining to various cases over which Judge Horton presided while Justice of the New York State Supreme Court, 6th Judicial District or as a private attorney. Includes typed charges to the jury, printed appeal books, and a few letters; also, correspondence and papers (1917-1919) relating to the Ithaca Calendar Clock Company, of which Horton was a trustee, mainly in connection with its going into receivership and with its dissolution.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Horton, Randolph, 1850-1929.; Ithaca Calendar Clock Company.; New York (State). Supreme Court (Sixth District)
Subjects:
Bankruptcy.; Law; Judges.; Lawyers.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Bishop, Anna H., Estate (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Broome County - Charges to Jury (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Broome County Supreme Court - Hon. Randolph Horton, Ithaca, N.Y. Charges (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
- Corbin, Edd W., Estate of (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Dassance, Mary A., Estate of (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Davis, Dewitt C., Estate of (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Fleming, Andrew J., Estate of (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Fleming, Mary E., Estate of (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Griffith, Anna F., Estate of (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ithaca Calendar Clock Company (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Jefferson, Lucy A., Papers: printed appeals and letters (Box 1, Folder 12)
- McKinney, James A., Estate of (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Pierson, A.C., Estate of (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Poole, Mary L. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Poyer, Aaron, Estate of (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Protts, Roger, Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Puff, Alice B., Estate of (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Quick, Martin A. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Ribble, Libbie, Matter (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Rothchild, Daniel, Estate of (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Solomon, Mike, Case (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Trapp, Earl J. - Bankruptcy matter (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Waverly (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Waverly Water Case (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Westmiller, Warren D., Estate of (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous documents (not in folder) (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Reprint from Ithaca Journal (undated) re: Horton's running for re-election as Justice, Supreme Court, 6th Judicial District (Democrat), Onetime Mayor of Ithaca 1909-1912(?); born Truxton 1850, lived in Cortland, Ithaca, attended Cornell; City Attorney; practiced law 1877-; circa. 1877-1928 (Box 2)
- Typed carbon copy of a 9 pp. Report to Randolph Horton, Ithaca Mayor, Apr. 15, 1909, From the Mayor's Committee of Citizens (Jacob Rothschild, Walter McCormick, Robert C. Osborn, Charles C. Howell, Joseph Campbell) who considered and investigated the question of erecting a Hospital for contagious diseases in the City of Ithaca and providing for its operation and maintenance. The Report also includes a summary of early hospital facilities, 1889-. (Box 2)
- Ithaca Calendar Clock Co. - bankrupt 1917
  - Co. Letterhead (samples)
  - Letters to Randolph Horton - Trustee for bondholders of I.C.C. - co. business (closing out - selling stock) - H.J. Bool Co., Inc. Ithaca, 1818-1819
  - List of bondholders of co.
  - Bills
  - Ithaca Silk Mills - account of mason work done for by D.B. & Co. (?)
  - Driscoll Bros. & Co., Ithaca - bill to I.C.C.
  - Summary of inventory 1917 (Oct. 1)
  - List of machinery formerly belonging to I.C.C.
  - Statement to bondholders ( 1917 ) re: financial status of Co. and decisions of bondholders regarding financial status
  - Copies of legal papers
  - 1918 - Letter to Jared T. Newman re: sale of machinery
  - Lists of equipment for sale
  - Letters to George W. Miller, President and General Manager
  - Copy of letter from George W. Miller ( 1917 ) explaining bitterly to a creditor in Boston why the Company went into receivership
  - Statement by Newman of best method of disposing of I.C.C.
  - Letter from J.T.N. to R.H.